[
    {"question" : "COVID-19 is a...",
        "answers" : ["Allergy", "Person", "Rule",  "Virus"],
        "correct" : 4
    },
    {"question" : "Which is not a symptom of the virus?",
        "answers" : ["Coughing", "Feeling Tired", "Laughing", "Feeling Hot"],
        "correct" : 3
    },
    {"question" : "Which is not a way I can protect myself from the virus?",
        "answers" : ["Washing my hands often", "Sharing snacks with friends", "Wearing a mask",  "Keeping a 2m distance from people"],
        "correct" : 2
    },
    {"question" : "Who can catch the virus?",
        "answers" : ["My grandparents", "My parents", "My friends", "Everyone"],
        "correct" : 4
    },
    {"question" : "What is quarantine?",
        "answers" : ["Drying off after a shower", "Having to stay home", "Not sleeping for a whole week", "Shopping for masks"],
        "correct" : 2
    },
    {"question" : "Why do I quarantine?",
        "answers" : ["To stop the virus from spreading", "To grow my  hair", "To make the virus feel lonely", "To make time go slower"],
        "correct" : 1
    },

    {"question" : "How long should I quarantine to be safe?",
        "answers" : ["2 Weeks", "1 Day", "3 hours", "9 Years"],
        "correct" : 1
    },

    {"question" : "What year was the first case of the virus discovered?",
        "answers" : ["2021", "2020", "2019", "2018"],
        "correct" : 3
    },

    {"question" : "Why do I need a vaccine?",
        "answers" : ["The virus is scared of needles", "Our body can fight the virus", "We'll get superpowers", "Viruses get sucked out"],
        "correct" : 2
    },

    {"question" : "What is not a side effect of the vaccine?",
        "answers" : ["Fever", "Feeling tired", "Pain in the arm", "Growing a beard"],
        "correct" : 4
    }
    
]